bandainamco-am.co.uk 2018-12-28

# 

## BANDAI NAMCO Amusement Europe Ltd Privacy Policy

Last Updated: May 2018

## Introduction

BANDAI NAMCO Amusement Europe Ltd respects the privacy rights of its customers. This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by us when you use our websites and other online products and services that contain this policy (the “Website”) or when you otherwise interact with us.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If you do not agree to the changes, please do not use our Website or otherwise provide us with your personal information.  Please review the Privacy Policy from time to time to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

**Collection of Information**

We collect different types of information about our Website users, including:

·       Information provided directly by you, including your name and contact information provided when you contact us regarding customer services, sales enquires and other enquiries. 

·       Browser type and language, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the websites visited before our Website; and

·       Information collected from other sources combined with information collected from you as necessary to perform our services.

**Use of Information**

We only collect, store and use your information if you have consented to itor, to the extent that it is necessary (i) for the performance of your agreement with us; (ii) to comply with our legal obligations; or (iii) for the purpose of our legitimate interests, including operating, evaluating and improving our business.

We use your information for the following purposes:

·       Provide, maintain, and improve the Websites

·       Provide and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information

·       Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;

·       Detect, investigate and/or prevent fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity;

·       For any other purpose required or authorized for us to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations; and 

·       For any other purpose for which you provided the information.

**Sharing of Information**

We do not share, sell, transfer or otherwise exchange your personal information with third parties, unless required for the provision of our products or services, otherwise in accordance with this Privacy Policy, or permitted by law or unless you have given us consent. We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:

·       With our employees, affiliates, related companies, vendors, consultants and third-party service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf or help us provide our services;

·       In response to legal process or a request for information if disclosure is in accordance with, or as otherwise required by, any applicable law, rule, or regulation;

·       In connection with any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and

·       With your consent or at your direction.

**Security and Storage**

We take reasonable technical and organizational measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access. Further, Personal information is stored only for as long as necessary to fulfil the purpose it was collected. Data will be de-identified or deleted if no longer needed, unless further storage is required by law.

**International Transfers**

Where we share or transfer data outside of the EEA, our collection, storage and use of your personal information will continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy, and we take such steps as are reasonable in the circumstances to ensure it is used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

Our Website uses cookies and other tracking technology to provide the Website as well as analyse and track usage. For more information, view our Cookie Policy [click here](http://www.bandainamco-am.co.uk/files/uploads/file-164.pdf).

## Children’s Data

Our Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 16, but if you learn we have collected information from your child without your consent, please contact us at the address below.  We will take reasonable steps to promptly erase such information from our records.

**Third Party Sites**

Our Website contains links to other websites or services operated by third parties.  Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to our Website and we cannot be responsible for personal information that third parties may collect, store and use. You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully.

## Data Protection Rights

You, and your legal guardian if you are a minor, may be able to exercise certain data protection rights under applicable law. Your rights under applicable law may include:

·       Access to the personal information we process about you as well as the right to data portability, 

·       The right to have personal information corrected or erased, 

·       The right to restrict the processing of your personal information

·       The right to withdraw your consent at any time for consent we have obtained from you, although this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing prior to the withdrawal. 

·       You also have the right to object, at any time, to the processing of your personal information which is based on our legitimate interests. 

·       Where we process your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you have the right to object at any time to such processing, including for profiling purposes to the extent that it is related to direct marketing. If you object to processing for direct marketing purposes, we will no longer process your personal information for such purposes. In that case we may still send you transactional or relationship messages, but only about our ongoing business relations.

To exercise these rights, you should make a request using our contact details set out below. If you are not satisfied with the way we handle your request, you may lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority in your country of residence.

### Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please contact us at: 

BANDAI NAMCO Amusement Europe Ltd 

37-39 Kew Foot Road 

Richmond 

TW9 2SS
